<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./1080 Snowboarding.v64</path>
		<name>1080: TenEighty Snowboarding</name>
		<desc>You’re taking a Tahoe 155 snowboard down a steep, bumpy incline at night and you’re about to top off an Indy Nosebone with a 360° Air, and you haven’t even left your living room!  You’re Playing 1080° (Ten Eighty) Snowboarding, a game so intense you’ll be brushing the snow off your goggles.  With five different boarders, eight different Lamar snowboards, more than 25 tricks, a Half-Pipe and six different courses, this is as close as you’ll get to the real thing without hopping on the next ski lift.

• Six game modes and courses!
• 2-Player simultaneous play!
• Over 25 different tricks!
• Compatible with Rumble Pak accessory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/1080 Snowboarding-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie.v64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<desc>Action and Puzzles and Bears. Oh My!

Trouble brews when Gruntilda the witch captures the unbearably beautiful cub, Tooty. But before the grisly hag can steal the bear’s good looks, big brother Banjo and his fine-feathered friend, Kazooie, join forces to stop her. Combining their 24 moves and special powers, Banjo and Kazooie will fend off armies of beasts. Bear and bird must hunt down the 100 puzzle pieces and 900 musical notes that will ultimately lead them to Gruntilda. However, miles of swamp, desert and snow and one bear of an adventure stand in their way.

• Soar over islands to scout out buried treasure.
• Brave past whirling blades in the belly of a mechanical shark.
• With some voodoo magic, transform into different creatures to gain special powers.
• Solve the puzzles of the ancients to unearth the cursed labyrinths.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Banjo-Kazooie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Tooie.v64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Tooie</name>
		<desc>Grunty returns—and that's bad news for Banjo and Kazooie! In this all-new adventure, combine everything you learned in the award-winning prequel, Banjo-Kazooie, with dozens of brand-new moves and abilities. Explore eight original worlds—like a monstrous factory and a dilapidated amusement park. Solve incredible puzzles that link those worlds together—sometimes you'll have to complete tasks in several worlds to solve a single puzzle!

• Divide and conquer! The bear and bird are back, and this time, they can split up and work alone.
• Play as Mumbo! Now you'll get to take control of the bone-headed shaman himself.
• Meet Humba Wumba! She'll transform Banjo into a number of objects, such as a walkin', talkin' statue or a tightie whitie shootin' washer.
• Four-player mini-games! Play over a dozen mini-games, including five different shootout modes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Banjo-Tooie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman Beyond - Return of the Joker.z64</path>
		<name>Batman Beyond: Return of the Joker</name>
		<desc>Will The Joker have the last laugh? A sleeker, deadlier Clown Prince of Crime is back from the past to terrorize Gotham City in Batman Beyond: Return of the Joker. When The Joker's recent attacks nearly bring about the demise of the aging Bruce Wayne, it's up to you to help Batman avenge his mentor and send The Joker back to the bottom of the deck... forever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Batman Beyond - Return of the Joker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Smash Brothers.v64</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
		<desc>It's a Bumpin', Bruisin', Brawlin' Bash! The many worlds of Nintendo collide in the ultimate showdown of strength and skill! Up to four players can choose their favorite characters - complete with signature attacks - and go at it in Team Battles and Free-For-Alls. Or venture out on your own to conquer the 14 stages in single-player mode. Either way, Super Smash Bros. is a no-holds-barred action-fest that will keep you coming back for more!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Smash Brothers-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman 64.z64</path>
		<name>Bomberman 64</name>
		<desc>The evil Altair is using the Omni Cube to drain the energy from Planet Bomber. With the aid of a mysterious helper, you must defeat Altair, and restore peace to Planet Bomber. In the Adventure mode, guide Bomberman through 24 areas of perilous conflict. Battle Altair's sinister allies, destroy their bases and put an end to the insane attack. The multi-player Battle mode offers endless hours of explosive action. Use the standard Bomberman character or create a custom one and save it to an N64 Controller Pak.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Bomberman 64-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brunswick Circuit Pro Bowling.z64</path>
		<name>Brunswick Circuit Pro Bowling</name>
		<desc>Choose one of the 13 genuine tournament bowlers and start the challenge! You're provided with real player animations and lanes, as well as different lane conditions and various bowling balls (genuine Brunswick!)! Full 3D environment brings the game to life, and all the tournament rules are available, even the Brunswick "Skins" game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Brunswick Circuit Pro Bowling-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19991223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Point Of View</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania.z64</path>
		<name>Castlevania</name>
		<desc>Take control of Reinhardt Schneider, a whip-toting Vampire Killer who has waited his whole life to meet his destiny, or Carrie Fernandez, a young girl with a strong magical presence who is mysteriously drawn to Dracula's evil Castlevania. It is their duty to seek out Castlevania and put an end to its residents' plans. What is your destiny?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Castlevania-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer, Entertainment Kobe</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness.z64</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Legacy of Darkness</name>
		<desc>Before Reinhardt Schneider and Carrie Fernandez confronted Dracula, a magical warrior embarked on a quest that would ultimately lead him to Dracula's lair. Take control of Cornell, a powerful werewolf, who is seeking out the evil minions responsible for his sister's disappearance. Armed with the power to morph from human to werewolf, Cornell is destined to rescure his sister from a sinister plan and rid the world of Dracula once and for all. Will he succeed or fail? Will the past unravel the future? Discover the legacy in this exciting prequel.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64.v64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<desc>K. Rool has kidnapped the Kongs! Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Ponytail Twirl. Even rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Donkey Kong 64-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike 64.v64</path>
		<name>Excitebike 64</name>
		<desc>Experience extreme MX! You grind your way through the hairpin turn, a wall of mud exploding in your wake. Your next jump launches you into the air - you pull off a spectacular double no-footed can-can and become an instant legend! In Excitebike 64, you'll find all the high-flying action, heart-stopping stunts and bone-jarring crashes of the extreme sport of motocross. It'll set the daredevil inside you free. 20 stadium tracks and awesome outdoor courses - plus six different riders with six unique styles!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Excitebike 64-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-zero X.v64</path>
		<name>F-Zero X</name>
		<desc>It's you against 29 other machines competing for the title of F-Zero X Champion. You're racing at speeds of over 1,000 km/h high above the atmosphere. Your competition comes from every corner of the galaxy and won't shed a tear at the thought of smashing you off the track. With four-player simultaneous gameplay and the Rumble Pak accessory, you have the fastest racing game on the N64 system!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/F-zero X-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980714T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GoldenEye 007.v64</path>
		<name>GoldenEye 007</name>
		<desc>You are Bond, James Bond.

You are assigned to covert operations connected with the GoldenEye weapons satellite.  M will brief you on your mission and objectives from London.  Q Branch will support your efforts with a plentiful supply of weapons and gadgets.  Moneypenny offers you light-hearted best wishes and you’re off!

Your mission begins in the heavily guarded chemical warfare facility at the Byelomorye Dam in the USSR.  Look and shoot in any direction as you navigate 12 interactive 3-D environments.  Use stealth and force as you see fit in matters of international security.  Consider the military personnel expendable.  You are licensed to kill!

* Exciting 3-D environments.
* Highly intelligent enemies!
* Numerous Q gadgets and weapons!
* Battery-backed memory saves game progress!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/GoldenEye 007-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Tetris Challenge.z64</path>
		<name>Magical Tetris Challenge</name>
		<desc>Join Disney's Mickey, Minnie, Donald and Goofy as they embark on a non-stop adventure full of challenging fun and excitement in Magical Tetris Challenge. Completely addictive, deceptively simple, you'll go wild in a kaleidoscopic shower of falling Tetris pieces in this magical version of the world's most popular video game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Magical Tetris Challenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64.z64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<desc>Three… Two… One… GO!  The signal light changes and you drop the pedal to the metal.  Take on up to three friends in the split-screen VS games, or race solo in the Mario GP.  Tell your friends to bring it on in the highly competitive Battle mode.  Advanced features allow you to race with your “Ghost”.  The driving data from your best run appears as a transparent character on the screen.  No longer must you simply race against the clock -- you can actually race against yourself!

* Save your hottest Ghost data to a portable N64 Controller Pak!
* Collect multiple power-up items!
* Twenty different courses -- 4 Cups with 4 courses each and 4 special Battle mode courses!
* Everyone’s favorite characters are back and gorgeously rendered, including two new additions, Donkey Kong and Wario!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Mario Kart 64-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Tennis.z64</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis</name>
		<desc>All of your favorite characters hit the court in a wild and wacky multiplayer tennis game from the makers of Mario Golf. Mario, Luigi, Bowser, Peach, Toad, and Donkey Kong lead off the all-star, 14-player line-up. The fast-paced action will have you unleashing vicious volleys, life-saving lobs, ballistic backhands and electrifying super-charged smashes!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Mario Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000721T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 64.z64</path>
		<name>Mega Man 64</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Volnutt is the game's playable character. Mega Man Volnutt is a "Digger", a person in charge of investigating ruins from a flooded Earth. During his journey with his friends, their ship crashes in Kattelox Island, where Mega Man decides to confront pirates who are attacking it to obtain the its hidden treasure. As an action roleplaying game, Mega Man Legends's gameplay is very different from the ones of the original series despite sharing a few elements.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Mega Man 64-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20001122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paper Mario.z64</path>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
		<desc>Mario pals around in an all-new action adventure! Mario's back in his first adventure since Super Mario 64, and this time, Bowser's bent on preventing a storybook ending. When Princess Peach is kidnapped, Mario plots to rescue the seven Star Spirits and rid the Mushroom Kingdom of Koopa's cruel cohorts. As he travels from the tropical jungles of Lavalava Island to the frosty heights of Shiver Mountain, he'll meet up with seven all-new companions... and he'll need help from each one or there'll be no happily ever after.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Paper Mario-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super_Mario 64.v64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<desc>Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3-D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive sound track, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis - Bowser, King of the Koopas!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Super_Mario 64-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask</name>
		<desc>Link’s all-new epic adventure lands him in the mystical world of Termina, where ever-present clocks count down the hours until a menacing moon falls from the sky above.  When his horse and Ocarina are stolen by a strange, masked figure, Link embarks on an urgent quest to solve the mystery of the moon, save the world from destruction, and find his way back to the peaceful land of Hyrule!

* Link transforms before your eyes--Over 20 magical masks give Link powers and abilities he’s never had before!  Watch him transform into a hapless Deku child, a mighty Goron hero and a legendary Zora guitarist.
* Race against time--Characters and events flow with the hours of the day.  Set your own schedule and even alter time itself in a race to stop the moon and save the world!
* Panoramic environments!  Powered-up action battles!  Fully interactive characters and events!  Experience gorgeous rendered landscapes, swarms of attacking enemies and a deep, engrossing world of wonders with the power of the N64 Expansion Pak.

Also Available
The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask Collector's Edition</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Legend of Zelda 2 - Majora's Mask.v64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask</name>
		<desc>Link’s all-new epic adventure lands him in the mystical world of Termina, where ever-present clocks count down the hours until a menacing moon falls from the sky above.  When his horse and Ocarina are stolen by a strange, masked figure, Link embarks on an urgent quest to solve the mystery of the moon, save the world from destruction, and find his way back to the peaceful land of Hyrule!

* Link transforms before your eyes--Over 20 magical masks give Link powers and abilities he’s never had before!  Watch him transform into a hapless Deku child, a mighty Goron hero and a legendary Zora guitarist.
* Race against time--Characters and events flow with the hours of the day.  Set your own schedule and even alter time itself in a race to stop the moon and save the world!
* Panoramic environments!  Powered-up action battles!  Fully interactive characters and events!  Experience gorgeous rendered landscapes, swarms of attacking enemies and a deep, engrossing world of wonders with the power of the N64 Expansion Pak.

Also Available
The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask Collector's Edition</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/The Legend of Zelda 2 - Majora's Mask-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time</name>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule.  He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce.  As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf’s evil schemes.  Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora’s Domain.  Before you complete this epic quest, you’ll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.

• The immersive storyline and environments draw players into an amazing 3D world.
• Time travel allows you to play as Link in different stages of his life.
• New gameplay features include a unique targeting system and 1st and 3rd person perspectives.
• Up to three games can be saved simultaneously to memory!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms - Armageddon.z64</path>
		<name>Worms Armageddon</name>
		<desc>Gameplay is turn-based, with each team moving in sequence (which is determined randomly) across two-dimensional terrain. During a single turn, a team can only move one of its worms (unless the Select Worm item is used). Worms can walk and jump, as well as (when the proper items are available) swing by rope, parachute, teleport, and bungee. The objective of a traditional match is to defeat all opposing teams by killing their worms, although in the campaign some missions have other objectives (such as collecting a specific crate).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Worms - Armageddon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990423T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team17</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
